<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://meticulousdetailing.ca/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://meticulousdetailing.ca/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://meticulousdetailing.ca/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>Meticulous Detailing Inc. - All Things Detailing</title>
  <updated>2020-07-06T13:19:00-07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Meticulous Detailing Inc.</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://meticulousdetailing.ca/blogs/news/introducing-p-s-iron-buster-wheel-paint-decon-remover</id>
    <published>2020-07-06T13:19:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-02-25T19:20:51-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://meticulousdetailing.ca/blogs/news/introducing-p-s-iron-buster-wheel-paint-decon-remover"/>
    <title>Introducing P&amp;S Iron Buster | Wheel &amp; Paint Decon Remover</title>
    <author>
      <name>Melody Parker</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p style="float: left;">P&amp;S has made another superb addition to the <a href="https://meticulousdetailing.ca/collections/double-black-renny-doyle-collection" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Double Black Diamond Renny Doyle Collection</a>. Meet Iron Buster Wheel &amp; Paint Decon Remover – a not too bad smelling iron remover. </p>
<p>Iron Buster is an acid free cleaner featuring:</p>
<ul>
	<li>low odour</li>
	<li>colour change</li>
	<li>fast action</li>
	<li>a pH balanced formula</li>
</ul>
<p style="float: left;">This product works to dissolve embedded iron particulates from wheels and painted surfaces. After application, Iron Buster quickly changes to a purple colour if iron particulates are plentiful. It can then be rinsed away, leaving behind a clean decontaminated surface. So easy!</p>
<p style="float: left;">When applying to paint surfaces, it’s best to wash and dry the surface prior to applying Iron Buster. Prewashing wheels, though, is not required.</p>
<p>Once the surface has been prepped (if applicable), spray apply a generous amount of Iron Buster and allow it so sit for 2-5 minutes. Do not allow it to dully dry on the surface though. Rinse thoroughly with water and voila! You’ll be busting that iron out of there in no time.</p>
<p>We LOVE this new product and can't get enough of it. If you'd like to try it yourself, we offer Iron Buster in pints or gallons <a href="https://meticulousdetailing.ca/products/double-black-renny-doyle-iron-buster" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
<p>For a fun demo, check out the video below!</p>
<p><br>
<iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/aAWw9VfdlYQ" width="560"></iframe></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://meticulousdetailing.ca/blogs/news/p-s-bead-maker-review-best-versatile-sealant</id>
    <published>2020-06-29T13:01:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-02-25T19:22:19-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://meticulousdetailing.ca/blogs/news/p-s-bead-maker-review-best-versatile-sealant"/>
    <title>P&amp;S Bead Maker Review | Best Versatile Sealant!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Melody Parker</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><a href="https://meticulousdetailing.ca/products/bead-maker-paint-protectant" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" title="Bead Maker P&amp;S">Bead Maker</a> is part of the Double Black Diamond Renny Doyle product line offered by P&amp;S. We use this product every day on our own vehicles and our customer’s vehicles – and they love it! Because of this, we are well versed in what Bead Maker has to offer, and what surfaces it can and can’t be used on.</p>
<h3>High Versatility</h3>
<p>We can not gush enough about the versatility of this product. Bead Maker is known for being one of the most adaptable products out there, and as such, it is a must have for any car detailing enthusiast.</p>
<p style="float: right;">This spray sealant cures and forms a semi-durable layer of film that is very slick and water-beading. It’s versatility extends to how it can be applied as well. Either spray directly on a surface and wipe dry, or spray it onto a towel and then wipe down. It can withstand direct sunlight, so using it on that sunny car show day is no problem at all for this sealant.</p>
<h3>Surface Friendly</h3>
<p>Originally it was developed for paint surfaces, so that is its number one use. But the strength of Bead Maker means it can be used on just about any surface including stripped paint surfaces, coatings, PPF, other paint sealants, and over waxes too.</p>
<p>The only surfaces it should <em>not</em> be used on are interior surfaces like cloth and carpet. However, it does very well on matte finishes and vinyl wraps. Bead Maker does not affect the look of a matte finish, and only adds a slick finish and beading property.</p>
<p>Either way, the versatility and high success rate of this product is what makes it so popular and you really can't go wrong with it. Convenient and simple to use, Bead Make is a must have for any professional detailer or DIY enthusiast. </p>
<p>We offer Bead Maker in pints or gallons <a href="https://meticulousdetailing.ca/products/bead-maker-paint-protectant" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>. To accompany your Bead Maker, grab one of our <a href="https://meticulousdetailing.ca/products/bead-maker-ultimate-towel" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bead Maker Ultimate Towels</a> and a <a href="https://meticulousdetailing.ca/products/ik-bead-maker-sprayer" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bead Maker Sprayer</a>.</p>
<p></p>
<table style="width: 100.592%;">
	<tbody>
		<tr>
			<td style="width: 45%; text-align: left;">
			<p><img alt="Bead Maker Sprayer" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0266/9880/9404/files/F143775085_large.png?v=1593460686" style="float: none;"></p>
			</td>
			<td style="width: 50.5921%;">
			<p></p>
			<p></p>
			<p></p>
			<p style="text-align: left;"><img alt="Bead Maker Ultimate Orange Towel" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0266/9880/9404/files/beadmaker_towel_large.png?v=1593460750" style="float: none;"></p>
			</td>
		</tr>
	</tbody>
</table>
<p></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://meticulousdetailing.ca/blogs/news/how-to-be-a-detailer-when-youre-a-perfectionist</id>
    <published>2020-06-15T11:01:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-02-25T19:23:11-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://meticulousdetailing.ca/blogs/news/how-to-be-a-detailer-when-youre-a-perfectionist"/>
    <title>How To Be a Detailer When You&apos;re a Perfectionist</title>
    <author>
      <name>Melody Parker</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Any perfectionist who has ever wanted to start a detailing business can relate to the struggles of overcoming their inner-critic. Auto detailing is about the details after all – but so is perfectionism.</p>
<p>Can anything ever truly be perfect though? Your perfectionist side would have you believe that yes, it can, and nothing else is acceptable. But while spending lots of time removing stains and scratches that you want to see gone may be great for your customer, is it good for you?</p>
<p>Being a perfectionist is by no means a bad thing; Lord knows there are unfortunately many detailers in the industry that offer subpar detailing services and their prices reflect this. Striving to offer quality results in an industry that relies on the highest quality output is a fundamental mindset for running your detailing business successfully.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, you may find yourself struggling with the battle of how much is too much. A key factor we have found to ensure quality results while being confident that a job is truly done, is to first master your craft.</p>
<h2>Master Your Craft</h2>
<p style="float: right;">Being confident in the tools, products, and techniques you use and knowing the expectations of them will help you identify when something isn’t working the way it should be. As with anything, this takes time and practice.</p>
<p style="float: right;"></p>
<p style="float: right;"></p>
<p style="float: right;"></p>
<p style="float: right;"></p>
<h2></h2>
<h2></h2>
<h2></h2>
<h2>Establish Boundaries</h2>
<p>Another key factor for overcoming your inner-perfectionist on a detailing job is to establish boundaries within your services. Boundaries imply expectations, and as long as you’ve met those expectations, you will keep your customer satisfied and can streamline your business for profit and quality.</p>
<p>At the end of the day, if the customer isn’t paying for every little scratch to be gone, you have to ask yourself why you are going over each section three of four times. Did the customer know beforehand those scratches were there? Did they know about those stains? How can they expect them to be gone if they didn’t even know they were there?</p>
<p>If you offer packages, has the customer been educated on exactly what each package includes? The more the expectations are defined, the easier it is for you to identify the boundaries on a job.</p>
<h2>Know Your Worth</h2>
<p>Which brings us to our final key factor in overcoming your inner-perfectionist: know your worth. Detailing is hard work! Your time and skills are worthy of being compensated fairly. If you think a job is going to take much longer than anticipated, stop and re-group with the customer on their expectations and desires so you don't spread yourself too thin and can still deliver what the customer wants.</p>
<p>Structure your business and services in such a way they ensure you and your employees are not constantly doing more work than what is being paid for. It’s easy to let the detailer in you dictate everything, but being a better businessperson first is crucial to running a successful detailing business that won't drain you and your resources. </p>
<p>For more tips, tricks, product reviews, and industry news on everything related to detailing, subscribe to our <a href="https://landing.mailerlite.com/webforms/landing/x9a6y7" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">monthly newsletter</a> and follow us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/meticulousdetailinginc/">Facebook</a> and <a href="https://www.instagram.com/meticulousdetailinginc/">Instagram</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
